What's with you?
Would you stop this nonsense already?
Usopp just got worked up because
things were moving too fast, right?
That's no reason to fight with your
own friend, especially when he's hurt.
If you give it some time, I'm sure
both of you will see how silly this is.
You've gone too far to turn back now.
That's not true.
There's nothing stopping you from
apologizing and talking it over one more time
Like I said no turning back and why not?
Usopp is willing to risk
his life to fight me.
He's more than just angry
Besides if just talking it over
was enough to make things right.
We wouldn't have come to
this in the first place
That's all I have to say so good night
luffy think about it you said
the Franky family came here
this afternoon right yeah so
what are you trying to say if
you hadn't let them off so easy
they wouldn't have stolen the
money from us in the first
place it's your fault those guys
attacked Usopp he's just freaking
out because he feels guilty
hey don't go blaming me for
not kicking their asses hard
enough you were the one who
ran off to go shopping what am
i supposed to cook if i don't
have any food both of you shut
There's been enough fighting already.
Whatever happened, it's
over now. Oh, I know.
But this wouldn't be happening
if it wasn't for him.
Oh, hey. You're back.
You were going after Usopp, weren't you?
Even if he was mad, I still
wanted to treat his wounds.
But he turned me away.
He found a place to stay, so
at least he can get some rest.
But do you know what he said to me?
He said we aren't friends now, so I should
leave him alone and go back to the ship.
Just this morning, we were
all so happy, and now what?
We lost Usopp.
Robin's still missing.
I feel like if we don't do something,
the whole crew is going to fall apart.
It's ten o 'clock.
Lusop will be here any second now.
Listen up!
I don't want any of you leaving the ship!
You got that?
Look!
Please don't fight!
so you didn't lose your nerve after all?
no matter how this battle
ends, you can't regret it.
this is exactly what you asked for!
that's perfect.
don't go easy on me.
i won't be the underdog this time.
in fact, i've already figured
out a way to defeat you.
shouldn't we stop this?
usap's injuries They're pretty bad.
If you can't stand to
watch, then go inside.
Make no mistake.
I'm not like any opponent
you've faced before.
We've been friends a long time.
I know all your powers, all your
strengths, and all of your weaknesses.
If you wake up in a dream, it will
be a place to go to the future.
So let's take a look at the same path.
We are one of them.
I have 8,000 men on my side!
If you don't surrender now,
I'll order them to attack!
What?
Why didn't he tell me?
Seriously, just go inside.
If you're gonna fight, then
at least take this seriously!
Ooh, Speed!
You have razor-sharp needles stuck
between all of your teeth! Ah!
It hurts just to imagine that!
I'm telling you, go inside.
You've got prickly cactus
spines under your finger!
Gum-Gum!
Pistol!
What happened?
Who's that?
Please don't die!
Special attack, Ketchup Star.
Pity for your enemy.
That's awfully arrogant, don't you think?
Flash dial!
Now, special attack, Eggstar!
Again, again, again!
Oh, it stinks! They're rotten!
Dammit, would you stop
messing around already?
You think this is a joke, huh?
Because I'm dead serious.
Oh, yeah? That's right.
This is the way I fight.
Careful, that gaping mouth
of yours is gonna get burnt!
Special attack, Tabasco Star!
What?
I wouldn't jump around
too much if I were you,
because the whole
battlefield is Keltrop Hell!
He's controlling the fight.
Listen, Luffy,
you can pity me if you want, but I'm
gonna beat you and take the Mary with me!
And I don't care what it takes!
Special attack, Pimpersaur!
Like I said, I know you, so I know
which attacks are gonna work the best!
Damn it!
This stuff stinks!
My mouth is burning!
And it hurts!
I'm not gonna give you
an itch, you hear me?
Special attack, Shiniken Shooting Star!
I'm using a breath dial.
You didn't notice the smell
because of the rotten eggs.
And now you're completely
surrounded by gas!
Gas?
Don't tell me he...
Sorry!
Flamescar!
That one's gonna sting!
I am Usopp, leader of the invincible nation
of pirates who reign over this island.
You stand before a living legend, the
most revered pirate who ever lived.
I am the great Captain Usopp!
That's pretty cool!
Shut your mouth or I'll
shut it for you! How come?
We're friends, right? So get on!
Hey!
I see an island!
Awesome!
I can't wait to check it out!
All right, let's go.
Mary, full speed ahead.
Full speed ahead.
I can't take this anymore. Luffy!
Luce up!
I'm no fool.
I realize it'll take more
than that to beat you.
I know you, Luffy.
You fight every battle
with all your strength.
But I'm ready for any
technique you've got.
Special attack!
Come, come!
Blasting...
Captain Stars!
Ah!
Triple exploding star!
Now Gawgawm!
It's Kaku!
It's time to put an end to this!
Gonzo!
Bazooka!
Hmm.
Recognize this?
I bet that bazooka would have hurt.
Let's find out!
Impact!
He used an impact dial!
I won't lose to you!
I am Usopp, leader of the Invincible Nation
of Pirates who reign over this island!
Cheers to a new ship and a new Gourmet!
So, how do you like this one?
Yeah, keep it. That's the one.
Okay, it's all done.
Now the Going Mary has everything
she could possibly need.
Com Com!
Usopp!
At least it's over now.
You idiot!
You knew it would end like this!
You knew you could never beat me!
Why did this have to happen?
Do whatever you want with them, Mary.
I won't let anything hold us back.
We're getting a new ship
and sailing forward.
Hey, let me sit up there!
Sorry, Usopp, but this seat's
reserved for the captain.
Oh, what are you making?
Let me see, let me see!
Hold on, the Usopp factory is
off-limits until I finish this for Nami.
Guys, listen up.
I will go to Elbas someday.
To the Village of Warriors!
Yeah, great!
It's the festival on the
night before gold hunting!
So long, Usopp.
It was fun!
While it lasted.
Chopper, leave him alone.
What are you saying?
He was already hurt before the fight If I
don't help him, who knows what'll happen?
He isn't part of our
crew anymore. So what?
I'm a doctor!
It's my doctor dream!
It's bad enough that he lost the duel.
If you pity him at a time like this,
you'll end up hurting him more
than any of those injuries.
I'm sure you have good intentions,
but all we can do now is
give him dignity and defeat.
He knew that when he challenged Luffy
to a duel, this is how it might end.
It's too much.
This is what it means to be captain.
You can't doubt yourself.
In times like these, if
you lose your confidence
Then who can we have faith in?
Let's pack our things and go.
You know as well as me.
That after tonight.
We can never return to this ship again?
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
Thank
you
so much for watching.